Willison, Malcolm; Papers apap055
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Economic Conversion, 1979-1994; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  - Article, "Dismantling the Cold War Economy", 1992 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 7)
  - Article, "Economic Conversion and Jobs: Is It Really Possible", 1994 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 8)
  - Article, "The Economics of Conversion", 1988 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 9)
  - Article, "Problems of Conversion from Military to Civilian Economy", 1985 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 10)
  - Article, "What We Learned in Arkansas", 1993 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 11)
  - Business Statistics, New York State Quarterly Summary, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 12)
  - Capital District-Berkshire Area Economic Conversion Study Group (CABEC), 1987-1988 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 13)
  - CABEC, Contact Lists, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 14)
  - CABEC, Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 15)
  - CABEC, Defense Jobs, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 16)
  - CABEC, Employee Ownership Project (EOP), 1988 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 17)
  - CABEC, Grant Opportunities, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 18)
  - CABEC, Minutes, Agendas, Notes, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 19)
  - CABEC, National Networks and Legislation, 1984-1988 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 20)
  - CABEC, New York State Proposed Legislation, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 21)
  - CABEC, Northeast Economic Diversification Conference (NEED), Berkshire Community College, Pittsfield, MA, 1989 April 22 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 22)
  - CABEC, NEED, April 22, 1989, Committee Meeting Minutes/Notes/Agendas, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 23)
  - CABEC, NEED, April 22, 1989, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 24)
  - CABEC, Northeastern New York Economic Diversification Conference, Siena College, Loudonville, New York, 1989 November 18 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 25)
  - CABEC, Economic Diversification Conference, November 18, 1989, Committee Meeting Minutes, Notes, Agendas, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 26)
  - CABEC, Economic Diversification Conference, November 18, 1989, Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 27)
  - CABEC, Regional Networking, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 29)
  - CABEC, Registration Cards, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 30)
  - CABEC, Statewide Networks and Coalitions, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 31)
  - The Census, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 32)
  - Center for Economic Conversion, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 33)
  - Center for Economic Conversion Positive Alternatives, 1987-1996 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 1981-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1990-1996; Undated (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 36)
  - Connecticut, 1985-1992 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 37)
  - Connecticut, "More Jobs, More Security: Alternatives for Military Dependent and Declining Basic Industries in Connecticut", 1985 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 39)
  - County Human Services Directory, Capital Region, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 40)
  - Defense Spending and Conversion, 1989-1994 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 41)
  - Democrats for Tax Justice, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 42)
  - Department of Labor, 1985; 1990-1993 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 43)
  - Department of Labor Albany/Schenectady/Troy Labor Area Summary, 1982-1988 (Box 1 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 44)
  - Department of Labor Labor Area Summary Monthly Statistical Report, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 1)
  - Department of Labor Labor Area Summary Monthly Statistical Report, 1990-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 2)
  - Department of Labor Labor Area Summary Quarterly Analytical Report, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 3)
  - Eastern Europe, 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 4)
  - Economic Conversion and Disarmament, 1983-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 5)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition of the Capital Region (ECCCR), 1986-1992 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 6)
  - Economic Conversion Coalition of the Upper Hudson (ECCUHR), 1990-1994 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 7)
  - Economic Development, Capital District, 1980-1983 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 8)
  - Economic Development, New York State, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 9)
  - Economic Development, New York State Legislation, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 10)
  - Economic Development, Regional, 1979-1983 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 11)
  - Energy, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 12)
  - Environment, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 13)
  - "From Fear to Friendship: A Celebration of Jews and Christians", 1986 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 14)
  - Gays in the Military, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 15)
  - General Electric, 1986-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 16)
  - Government, 1988-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 17)
  - Guide to 1987 Economic Censuses and Related Statistics, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 18)
  - INFACT, Nuclear Weapons Campaign, 1985-1990 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 19)
  - The Intercollegiate Review, 1985 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 20)
  - International Economic Conversion Conference, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 21)
  - Knolls Action Project, 1986-1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 22)
  - Labor-Religion Coalition, 1985-1990 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 23)
  - March on Washington, 1989 April 29 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 24)
  - Massachusetts, 1986-1987; 1995 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 25)
  - Melkonian, Martin and Margaret, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 26)
  - Minnesota, 1984 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1994 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 28)
  - Mow, Carolyn, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 29)
  - Newsletter Employment in NYS, 1991-1996 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 30)
  - Newsletter The New Economy, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 31)
  - Newsletter Space and Security News, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 32)
  - Newsletters (General Electric News), 1981; 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 33)
  - Newsletters (Plowshare Press), 1986-1987 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
  - New York State Science and Technology Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Arms, 1988-1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 2)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), 1988-1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 3)
  - Pathways to Peace, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 4)
  - Peace Action, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 5)
  - Peace Associates, Inc., 1985-1990 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 6)
  - Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 7)
  - Report, "Alternatives to Military Production at Unisys Plants in Minnesota", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 8)
  - Report, "The Arms Race: Illusion of Security", 1978 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 9)
  - Report, "Bankrupting America: The Tax Burden and Expenditures of the Pentagon by Congressional District", 1984 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 10)
  - Report, "Briefing Book on the Military-Industrial Complex", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 11)
  - Report, "Building America's Future: Alternatives to Economic Decline", 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 12)
  - Report, "Charging the Future: Converting the St. Louis Economy", 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 13)
  - Report, "A Citizen's Guide to Promoting Toxic Waste Reduction", 1990 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 14)
  - Report, "Continuity and Change in US-Korean Relations", Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 15)
  - Report, "Conversion and Reindustrialization Alternatives to Pentagon Industrial Policy I", 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 16)
  - Report, "Conversion and Reindustrialization Alternatives to Pentagon Industrial Policy II", 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 17)
  - Report, "Converting the Work Force: Where the Jobs Would Be", Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 18)
  - Report, "Defense Technology Conversion Reinvestment and Transition Assistance", 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 19)
  - Report, "Destructive Investment: Nuclear Weapons and Economic Decline", Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 20)
  - Report, "Economic Conversion: Indispensable for America's Economic Recovery", 1989 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 21)
  - Report, "Economic Conversion and International Inspection: Alternatives to Arms Exports and Militarism", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 22)
  - Report, "A Few Billion for Defense", 1985 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 23)
  - Report, "How Big Is the Military Economy?", 1988 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 24)
  - Report, "Hydro-Quebec Draft Generic Environmental Review", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 25)
  - Report, "Hydro-Quebec Economic Study: Draft Report", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 26)
  - Report, "The Impact of Defense Contracting in NYS and Its Economic Development Region, 1987-1990", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 27)
  - Report, "An Introduction to Economic Conversion", 1988 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 28)
  - Report, "Is Depression the Price of Peace?", 1988 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 29)
  - Report, "Military Base Closures", 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 30)
  - Report, "The Military in Your Backyard: How to Determine the Impact of Military Spending in Your Community", 1984 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 31)
  - Report, "Military Spending: An Occupational Hazard", 1984 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 32)
  - Report, "The New American Agenda: Economic Conversion for Jobs, Prosperity and Development", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 33)
  - Report, "New Challenges in Education and Training of the European Workforce", 1990 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 34)
  - Report, "Putting Communities in Control", 1984-1994 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 35)
  - Report, "Reindustrialization from Below", Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 36)
  - Report, "Reinvest in New York: Put Our Federal Tax Dollars to Work", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 37)
  - Report, "The Right Choice for New York: A Fair Tax System for Fiscal Stability and Growth", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 38)
  - Report, "A Shift in Military Spending to America's Cities", 1988 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 39)
  - Report, "A Short Primer for Partisans on How a Bilateral Nuclear Weapons Freeze Could Help Revitalize the Ailing American Economy", 1983 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 40)
  - Report, "Star Wars: The Economic Fallout", 1987 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 41)
  - Report, "The States and Economic Conversion: An Inventory and Recommendations for State Legislation", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 42)
  - Report, "Successful Conversion Experiences", 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 43)
  - Report, "Technology and Economic Performance", 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 44)
  - Report, "Trade Crisis: Time for Action", Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 45)
  - Report, "The Transnational Economy", 1982 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 46)
  - RFP, Dislocated Workers Innovative Strategies Demonstration Project, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 47)
  - San Diego Economic Conversion, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 48)
  - SANE/FREEZE, 1989-1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 49)
  - Schenectady Inner City Ministry, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 50)
  - Schenectady MLK Jr. Coalition, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 51)
  - Science for Peace, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 52)
  - Siena College, Peace Studies Program, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 53)
  - Somalia, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 54)
  - State Communities Aid Association (SCAA), 1981 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 55)
  - Statewide Emergency Network for Social and Economic Security (SENSES), 1987-1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 56)
  - The 21st Century Project, Undated (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 57)
  - USA Statistics in Brief, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 58)
  - Watervliet Arsenal, 1989-1994 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 59)
  - Watervliet Arsenal, "Diversification Study Final Report", 1993 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 60)
  - William Sloan Coffin Visit, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Economic Conversion), Folder 61)
- Lantz-Willison and Associates, 1961-1985; 5; 1 cubic ft.
  This series contains information about some of the projects that L-W Associates were engaged in. Though limited, series 5 includes L-W Associates' work with American Women in Small Businesses, Asia, the Disarming Images Study Circle, education, housing, the Law, Order and Justice Center, nuclear arms, environmental issues, the Radical Education Project, race, missile defense, transportation and urban studies.
  - American Women in Small Businesses, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 1)
  - Asia, 1968-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 2)
  - Disarming Images Study Circle, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 3)
  - Education, 1961-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 4)
  - Housing, 1973-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 5)
  - Lantz and Willison, Undated (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 6)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, 1981-1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 7)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Community Dispute Settlement, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 8)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Comprehensive Offender Employment Resource System (COER), 1978-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 9)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 10)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Funding Sources, 1980-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 11)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Halfway House Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 12)
  - Law, Order and Justice Center, Schenectady County Jail, 1979-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Arms, 1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 14)
  - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), Report Briefs, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 15)
  - PCBs in the Hudson River, 1979-1982 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 16)
  - Politics, 1972-1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 17)
  - Race, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 18)
  - Radical Education Project, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 19)
  - Reform Study Group, 1974 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 20)
  - RPI, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 21)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 22)
  - Social Indicators, 1952; 1973-1985 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 23)
  - Solid Waste, 1973-1983 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 24)
  - Star Wars, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 25)
  - Transportation, 1972-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 26)
  - Union College, 1967; 1971; 1982; 1986 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 27)
  - Urban Studies, 1960-1975 (Box 1 (5-Lantz-Willison and Associates), Folder 28)
- Economic and Social Action, 1958-1997; 6; 3.2 cubic ft.
  Series 6 is an assortment of information about various organizations and activities in the Capital Region. The economic and social activities in this series concern issues of poverty, nuclear disarmament, peace, economic conversion and neighborhood improvement. Some of the issues and/or groups are discussed in more detail in other series. There is some rich information and documentation about economic and social action groups in the region like the Neighborhood Action Coalition of Troy (N-ACT), The Capital District Transportation Committee (CDTC), The Clean Air/Transportation Committee (CA/T), Schenectady 2000, and the Saratoga Peace Alliance (SPA). There is also oversized material available in this series of maps that refer to the Schenectady 2000 development project.
  - Albany County Opportunity, Inc., 1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 1)
  - The Association for the Protection of the Adirondacks, Inc., 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 2)
  - Breaking the Cycle of Failure, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 3)
  - Capital District Community Loan Fund, 1987-1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 4)
  - Capital District Labor-Religion Coalition, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 5)
  - Capital District Regional Planning Committee, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 6)
  - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 7)
  - Capital District Transportation Committee, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 8)
  - Capital District Transportation Committee, Photos, Undated (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 9)
  - Center for Change/Coalition on Social Action, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 10)
  - Center for Change/Coalition on Social Action, It's Our Economy Conference, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 11)
  - Center for Environmental Options, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 12)
  - Center for Popular Economics, 1980 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 13)
  - The Challenge of Peace: God's Promise and Our Response, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 14)
  - Citizens Convention for Better Schools in Schenectady, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 15)
  - Clean Air/Transportation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 16)
  - Clean Air/Transportation Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 17)
  - Coalition for Post Cold War Concerns, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 18)
  - Committee on Environment and Public Works, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 19)
  - Committee for War, Peace and the Economy, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 20)
  - Communes, Undated (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 21)
  - Cooperative Self Reliance Campaign, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 22)
  - Economic Conversion, 1990-1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 23)
  - Economic Conversion, News Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 24)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, After the Cold War: Living with Lower Defense Spending, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 25)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Building a Peaceful Economy, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 26)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Capitol Hill Moves on Conversion, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 27)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Conversion Authorization and Appropriations, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 28)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Conversion and the Environment, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 29)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Defense Authorization, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 30)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Defense Budget Project, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 31)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Defense Spending and Its Economic Impact on New York State's Economy, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 32)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Federal Spending, 1990 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 33)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Making Peace Possible, 1989 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 34)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Memorandum in Support, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 35)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Military Base Closures, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 36)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Prime Contract Awards, 1993 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 37)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, Reinvest in Our Communities, 1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 38)
  - Economic Conversion, Report, War and Peace and the Environment, Undated (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 39)
  - Economic and Urban Development, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 40)
  - The Economy, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 41)
  - Ed Bloch for Congress, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 42)
  - Empire State Family Farm Alliance, 1980-1981; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 43)
  - The Environment, 1995 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 44)
  - Ground Zero, 1982 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 45)
  - Hill-Vale Neighborhood Based Association (NBA), 1992-1995 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 46)
  - Rick Hind Campaign, 1978 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 47)
  - Hiroshima-Nagasaki Remembrance, 1983; 1996 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 48)
  - Honest Weight Food Cooperative, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 49)
  - The ICA Group, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 50)
  - Labor Party Advocacy, 1996 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 1)
  - Lamoreaux Foundation, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 2)
  - Lamoreaux Foundation, Operation Crossroads, 1981 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 3)
  - Latin America, 1982-1996 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 4)
  - March 19th Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 5)
  - March 19th Coalition, Jobs/Economy Subcommittee, 1995 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981-1996 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous, News Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 8)
  - Movement for a New Society, 1979-1983 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 9)
  - Neighborhood Action Council of Troy (N-ACT), 1982-1987 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 10)
  - Neighborhood Action Council of Troy (N-ACT), Community Development Credit Union, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 11)
  - Neighborhood Action Council of Troy (N-ACT), Federal Funding, 1981-1986 (Box 2 (6-Economic and Social Action), Folder 12)